Jacob Namhyung Kim

Frontend Developer React | React Native

Contact

Address Burnaby, BC V5H 1R2

Phone 1-236-838-5758

E-mail everywherejacobkim@gmail.com

Skills

TypeScript

JavaScript

React.js

Next.js

Node.js

React Native

Tailwind CSS

GraphQL

REST API

CMS management

Teamwork and Collaboration

Organization and Time Management

Languages

English - Fluent

Korean - Fluent

Diploma in Korean English Interpretation & Translation

Self-motivated developer adds high level of experience over 2 years collaborating and working with team on multiple web and mobile agile projects. Passionate, hardworking coder with penchant for developing customized interfaces that factor in unique demands for design and accessibility. Focused on creating clean, robust code with exceptional security. Ready to help the team achieve company goals!

.....

Linkedin /everywherejacobkim | Github /everywherejacobkim

Work History

2023-01 -Current

Front End Developer

Homechow.ca, Vancouver, BC

- Developed responsive UI components using Typescript and Next.js, ensuring optimal user experience across mobile and desktop platforms.
- Utilized Cypress to debug tests and managing UI components using Storybook.

2022-08 -2023-01

Web Developer

Hope Village & ISU Inc, Yeongcheon, South Korea

- Updated old code bases to modern development standards improving functionality.
- Led the design and development of a new homepage, creating a visually engaging and responsive, user-friendly experience.

2015-01 -2020-12

Program Coordinator / Technical Administrative Assistant

Consulate general of the republic of Korea, Seattle, WA, USA

- Organized and managed cultural and educational programs from conception through successful execution.
- Analyzed website traffic and developed content to meet needs and interests of public website visitors.

Education

2021-05 -2022-12

Post-Degree Diploma: Web And Mobile App Design And Development

Langara College - Vancouver, BC

Bachelor of Science: Education Technology

Hanyang University - Seoul, South Korea

Projects

- Handy Chef | Mobile App | React native | MERN | Crossplatform mobile app which connects independent chefs with clients to bring a private restaurant experience to the clients' homes at an affordable rate (www.handychef.ca, 2022.01-04)
- Pomodee | Web App | React.js | MERN | Fun-and-network-driven timer app based on pomodoro technique which connects with others to collaborate in real-time study & work sessions (pomodee.com, 2022.05-08)
- My Travel Story | Web App | Next.js | GraphQL | Travel diary web app that allows users to publish travel memories and interact with other users (2022.09-12)